all righty today the challenge the
financial stealth hidden UI
unintimidating and no lockpicks so we've
got a drill again with Precision
Drilling but once again we've got
unintimidating and hidden UI hdden UI is
not that bad unintimidating is really
the worst part because that means we're
going to actually have to hack a
computer for this yep and also I'm
pretty sure I've L that camera so we're
going to back this body and get right
out of there because I was not careful
going up here and we won't even know
because it's hidden UI that is not a
good way of doing it let's just run down
there since no one's going to show up
over there
probably you know what yeah we should
probably just back off grab the disguise
over here and then not worry about
it cyber did you also
adj right then that's not a god taken
care of I suppose
which I mean sure
now all we got to do
it this is too good this is literally
too
good you turn yourself in that direction
right never mind we'll just leave the
camera regardless I mean otherwise we
would have just taken all that guard
we'll rewire this power box and then
afterwards we'll deal with the remaining
power boxes and probably also the god at
this rate so that's exactly what we're
going to do
we will completely ignore this C because
that is absolutely not helpful to us and
you know what we'll seize the
opportunity and knock that guard out in
the perfect
location cyber's got a l power box
actually which means that what I'm going
to do is I'm going to go up here run
past that camera for absolutely no
reason or actually a very good reason
which is
to not getting caught by those two I
mean that's literally the worst
combination to be caught by regardless
we get this door completely open cyber
should probably loot that camera at some
point because it's going to help us out
a lot and actually because I'm about to
open this
door
so you know what we'll Loop it it's fine
we'll go backwards we'll go past this
and we Loop that camera and it's going
to go just fine we've got a god there
but we don't have to worry about it the
guard's not going to care I
mean the guard would see the open
doorway except for one small
caveat the door is blocking the god from
seeing the open doorway and therefore
detecting the broken
door which is certainly not a way I mean
it's certainly a good way of not getting
caught and I'm not going to complain
about it so we'll go past all of that
and we will
right then we'll go back through here
hope we will hope that there are no Gods
over here to mess with us we'll start
with this photograph of
course and it seems to be going well and
now all we got to do is not get caught
by Ryan or any of the remaining Gods
over there
which it's harder than it seems because
that's exactly what's happening right
now so
instead why
Ryan no you're not doing that all right
just to make it
clear never mind you are doing that
there's not much I can do about it so
we'll go back over here and we will this
is actually perfect I
mean all right
we're going to go past all of this it's
going to be okay and we're going to get
the safe location and we'll take
advantage of it to open up the
safe so once the photographs remov we'll
open up the safe grab the hard drive and
now all we got to do is find Ryan
which won't be really which won't be
difficult at
all absolutely worth it I mean that got
almost
got Le but we should be fine now really
all we got to do right now is do
this the safe door is being a major
Nuance over here but I think I I'm still
able to do it so Ryan look at me over
here do me a favor and walk over here
and just in
time right then we are grabbing this bag
and we are getting right out of here I
mean it's probably a good idea
regardless so that's exactly what we're
going to do we're going to leave this
area and cyber the doors open over here
you might just want to leave through
that and that's the daily challenge in
just under 5
minutes I mean that ending wasn't
exactly too plann but it worked so I'm
not going to complain about that cheers
everyone have a great time
[Music]
oh